question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the "
                 "video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center "
                 "because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; "
                 "stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
]
